(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)My point is,
pretending to be an alien is
(Sheldon:)a valuable coping mechanism
I've used many times.
(Sheldon:)I did it the first time
I went to see you in a play.
(Sheldon:)You had no idea
Commander Umfrumf
(Sheldon:)of Ceti Alpha Three
was in the audience.
Oh, d-don't worry,
he gave you seven thumbs up.
(Penny:)Here's a question--
(Penny:)as an alien pretending to be
human, are you planning
(Penny:)to engage in any post-prom
mating rituals with Amy?
(Sheldon:)There are post-prom
mating rituals?
(Penny:)Not always.
(Penny:)Unless your date drives
a van with an air mattress,
(Penny:)then always.
(Sheldon:)Well, if it's part of the prom
experience, then I'm open to it.
(Penny:)You're kidding.
(Sheldon:)I may be an alien,
but I have urges.
(Sheldon:)If Amy wants to copulate
by firing her eggs into space,